

Ali Navidi

Sari, Iran → +989339668289

2 years of experience
ali_navidi24@yahoo.com
Portfolio: westernal.me/
Blog: dev.to/westernal

westernal 🕠
ali-navidi-850a80209 🛅
westernal 🐓
ali-navidi 🖹

Junior Front-End Developer

A highly motivated 4-year BSc. Computer Engineering student interested in frontend web developing with high team-working and punctuality ability eager to further knowledge and experience with professionals in the related field.

Skills: (Next.js JavaScript SEO Git Bootstrap Remix **c**) React.js HTML CSS TypeScript Node.js Cypress Express.js MongoDB Svelte Java Tailwind GraphQL Python

Experience

Restarone Solutions Inc. restarone.com

Sep 2022 to Dec 2022

Frontend Engineer Toronto, Canada

Frontend developer Tehran, Iran

Oben Origin co.

Jan 2020 to Nov 2021

Projects

social-media-frontend

www.westernal.net/ github.com/westernal/social-media-frontend

Westernal: a full stack social media based on songs

CSS, JavaScript, Cypress, Next.js

social-media-backend

Westernal: a full stack social media

JavaScript, Express.js, MongoDB, Node.js

Cinema

github.com/westernal/Cinema

Watching and downloading movies website and progressive web app (PWA) with Next.JS and TypeScript

TypeScript, CSS, JavaScript, Next.js

sari-sarte

Sari-sartel: a mobile and accessories shop.

JavaScript, CSS, Next.js

Dashboard

 $Admin\,dashboard\,using\,Next\,JS$

JavaScript, CSS, Next.js

Education

Noshiravni University of Technology nit.ac.ir

Oct 2018 to Feb 2023

Bachelor's of Science, Computer Engineering

Publications

Introducing Westernal: A social media based on songs

DEV Community

dev.to/westernal/introducing-westernal-a-social-media-based-on-songs-1pa9

How do you write your CSS?

DEV Community

dev.to/westernal/how-do-you-write-your-css-3pg2

Languages

Farsi Native

English Advanced